

8 White Street, Cork, Ireland

□+33 6 99 78 19 49 | ► rudy.murer.pro@gmail.com | 🏕 rudymurer.com | 🖫 murerr | 🛅 Murerr

Personal Profile

An eager, logical and detail focused Software Developer with 2+ years of experience. Wide-ranging expertise in Web development, Android and Object-Oriented Programming.

Technical Skills

PHP Used PHP daily for server-side applications at ForWare.

JavaScript Worked on front-end JavaScript applications at ASA Marketing.

Vue.js Produced modern user interface client-side with Vue.js.

Android Facilitated Android applications at Cansii, CIT and for personal projects.

Kotlin Used the kotlin language for severals Android application and Hackathon events.

Java Carried out small projects during the OOP Modules in France and Ireland.Python Made Python scripts to automate regular processes at ASA Marketing.

CI Tools Deployed projects using pipelines with Gitlab, Travis and Jenkins.

Work Experience

Full Stack Software Developer

Cork, Ireland

ASA MARKETING & FORWARE

Apr. 2019 - Now

- Facilitated and hosted a Web application using Firebase.
- Implemented a realtime fleet tracking system with Google Maps.
- Designed and developed a UI to filter and sort artworks.
- Learnt to prioritize my missions by using an issue tracking system.

Android Internship

Châteauneuf-sur-Isère, France

CANSII Apr. 2018 - Jun. 2019

- Developed a mobile application using Kotlin for MenuOnline web users.
- Used a RESTful API to synchronize data.
- Retrieved data from the end-point with Retrofit.
- Understood the importance of CI tools and Unit testing with Robotelectric.

PHP Internship

Crest, France

8 FABLAB

Apr. 2017 - Jun. 2017

- Created a client-side interface for customers to book a training session.
- Carried out an administration panel to manage the bookings using Dolibarr ERP.
- Billed customers using Stripe API.

Education_

BSc in Software Development

Cork, Ireland

2018 - 2019

CORK INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

Final Year Project: Transport AI

- Developed a mobile and web application to book the nearest self-driving car.
- The data was stored and retrieved using Firebase.
- Google Maps API was used to display user location.

RUDY MURER · CURRICULUM VITAE

1

DUT InformatiqueValence, France

Université Grenoble Alpes

(A two year university Diploma in Computing)

Final Year Project: Reprography App

- Established a web application that handle photocopies requests.
- The project was carried out using Symfony Framework.
- Learnt the importance of the Model View Controller.

Baccalauréat STI2D SIN

Valence, France

LYCÉE DES CATALINS

2015

2015 - 2018

(Leaving Certificat equivalent with special emphasis on Programming & Engineering.)

Additional Work Experience _____

Crest, France

McDonald's

Jan. 2017 - Aug. 2018

- Worked in a fast-paced environment.
- Followed procedures for safe food preparation, assembly and presentation.
- Anticipated customer's needs by communicating clearly with coworkers and management.

Skills Profile _____

Language

• French: Native language

• English: Fluent

• Italian: Limited working proficiency

Workplace Skills

- Creative problem solving: enjoy challenging tasks and finding new ways to do things.
- Excellent teamwork skills developed in Cansii & ForWare.
- Effective communications skills from part time jobs and ASA Marketing stand up meetings.

intrests_

Voluteer Work Eurre, France

MEMBER 2015 - 2016

- Organization of French events and festivals in my hometown community hall.
- Taught IT skills to seniors.

Extracurricular Activity

HOBBIES

- · Rock-climbing & Kayaking
- Rubik's cube & Board Games (Chess, Magic TCG, Warhammer 40k)
- DeepMind & Open Al

Referees

ForWare Joady Sinnot, IT Manager of ForWare, joady.sinnot@forware.ie

ASA Marketing Michelle Johnson, CEO of ASA Marketing, michelle.johnson@asamarketing.ie

CIT Colin Manning, Server-side devlopement teacher, colin.manning.ie

Cansii Cedric Angeniol, CEO of Cansii, cedric.angeniol@cansii.com